National Organization for Women, Albany Chapter; Records apap174
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
National Organization for Women--Albany, N.Y. Chapter Records
1971-2005
1972-1973
1973-
1976-1977
1977
1978-1979
1979-1981
1981
1981-1983
1983-1984
1986-1987
1987-1988
1988-1989
1989-1992
1993-1996
1997-
2006-
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
National Organization for Women--Albany (N.Y.) Chapter
apap174
5.0 cubic ft.
The National Organization for Women--Albany, N.Y. Chapter Records document the daily activities and special events involving the chapter as well as the chapter's interactions with the state and federal organizations.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this manuscript group were donated to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives by the National Organization for Women--Albany, NY Chapter in October 2005.
Biographical Sketch
The Albany Area National Organization for Women (NOW) is a grassroots, civil rights organization concerned with issues of and related to women. The chapter serves the Capital Region including Albany, Rensselaer, and Schenectady Counties. The National Organization for Women was founded in 1966 and has maintained its position on bringing equality to all women. Albany Area NOW belongs to a larger community whose main objective is to eliminate discrimination in the work place, school, the justice system, and all sectors of society.
The Albany chapter was one of the first local chapters in the State of New York to be in full operation (January 1972). From the time of its organization in the Capital Region, the chapter has made an effort to ensure woman have the same privileges and responsibilities as men within American society. There were originally plans to establish a chapter in the Capital Region in 1967, but there were financial setbacks in the state chapter that initially prevented the chapter's organization. The Albany chapter flourished quickly and was fortunate to have several leaders, including Sue Stevens Larsen, Pauline Brundage, and Jeanne Dross, who worked to build a strong foundation. These members occupied positions in the local and state NOW organizations. At various times in its history, the Albany chapter also served as the central office for NOW New York State.
NOW has been an advocate of reproductive rights and believes that reproductive issues are a matter of life and death for women. NOW also has supported educational opportunities for women, the ERA (Equal Rights Amendment), equal pay for women, gay and lesbian rights, rape prevention, and other key issues.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes administrative, including correspondence, minutes, by-laws, financial reports and conference materials, and subject files on women's issues, pertaining to the National Organization for Women (NOW) with particular strength in documenting the Albany and New York State chapters. The records of this women's organization pertain to sexual discrimination in education and employment, reproductive rights, gay and lesbian rights, the Equal Rights Amendment, and other gender-related issues.
Please see the records of NOW--New York State (APAP-029) for related materials.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series:
All series are arranged alphabetically.
Women; Social Activists and Public Advocates; Human Sexuality and Gender Identity; Albany, New York; Abortion services--New York (State)--Law and legislation; Women's rights--New York (State); Birth control--New York (State); Correspondence; By-laws; Newsletters; Minutes; Photographs; National Organization for Women; National Organization for Women--Albany (N.Y.) Chapter
- Administrative Files, 1972-2005; Undated; 1; 2.25 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  The series contains administrative materials created at the chapter, regional, state and national levels of the National Organization for Women. This includes meeting minutes, by-laws, financial reports, conference materials, legislative and lobbying files, task force materials and correspondence. The national, regional and statewide materials were acquired and retained at the local level, many by Sue Stevens Larsen, an Albany Area Chapter president in the late 1970s and early 1980s. The Albany Area NOW Chapter files consist of event flyers, press releases, correspondence, meeting minutes and newspaper clippings which document day-to-day activities. Please note that the New York State Council Meeting files may include just meeting materials for some years, while folders for other years contain plans, possibly discussed at meetings, event materials, and correspondence. At this is how the organization arranged the files, archivists retained this original order.
  - Administrative Policy Manual, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - Albany Area NOW Chapter, 1972 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Albany Area NOW Chapter, 1972-1973; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Albany Area NOW Chapter, 1976-1978; 1980-1982; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Albany Area NOW Chapter, 1983; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Albany Area NOW Chapter, 1996-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Albany Area NOW Chapter, Minutes and Notes, 1979-1980 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Albany Area NOW Chapter, Minutes and Notes, 1987; 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - Albany Area NOW Chapter Sign-in Meeting Sheets, 1994-1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - Application (blank) for Provisional Chapter Charter, Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - At-Large, Added Members, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - At-Large Delegate Election, 1977 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - By-Laws, Model Information, 1978; 1980; 1983; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - By-Laws, National, 1976 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - By-Laws, National, 1976; 1989; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - By-Laws, New York State and Northeast Region, 1977; 1983; 1991; 1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15)
  - Campaign Material for National Offices, 1977; 1982; 1985-1987; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 16)
  - Campaign Material for New York State and Northeastern Region Offices, 1986-1988; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - Chapter Chartering and Development, 1982-1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, 1981-1985; 1989-1991 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence Between Different NOW Chapters, 1976; 1983-1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - Fundraising, 1985-1986; 1988-1990; 1993; 1995-1996; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22-23)
  - "How to do a Vote Count", 1983 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - Internal Affairs, 1976 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - Issues Policy Manual, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - Legislative Priorities, National, 1975-1978; 1989 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - Legislative Program, 1977-1979 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - Legislative Program, 1980-1984 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - Lobby Day, 1979 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - Lobby Day, 1980 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - Lobby Day, 1981 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - Lobby Day, 1982 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - Lobby Day, 1983 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - Lobby Day, 1984 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - Lobby Day, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - Lobbying Efforts, Legislative Priorities, New York, 1977-1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - Lobbying Hints/Tips, 1982; 1984; 1992; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - Lobbyist, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 39)
  - Membership Applications and Correspondence, 1976; 1988; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 40)
  - Membership Lists, 1973; 1975-1979; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 41)
  - Membership Processing Manual, 1985 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 42)
  - NOW National, 1996; Undated (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 43)
  - NOW National Board Minutes, 1975-1976; 1978-1979 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 44)
  - NOW National Conference, 1975 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 45)
  - NOW National Conference, 1977 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 46)
  - NOW National Conference, 1978 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 47)
  - NOW National Conference, 1979 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 48)
  - NOW National Conference, 1981 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 49)
  - NOW National Conference, 1983-1985 (Box 1 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 50)
  - NOW National Conference, 1987; 1989-1992 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - NOW National Mailings, including Board Meeting Agendas, 1975-1976; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - NOW New York State, 1994-1998 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - NOW New York State, Archives, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - NOW New York State Child Care Task Force, 1984; 1987; 1989 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - NOW New York State Conference, 1974-2005 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - NOW New York State Conscious Raising Task Force, 1980-1981; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 8)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1977 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 9)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1978 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 10)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1979 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 11)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1980 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 12)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1981 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 13)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1982 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 14)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1983 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 15-16)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1984 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 17)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 18)
  - NOW New York State Council Meetings, 1987-1988 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 19)
  - NOW New York State Domestic Relations Law Task Force, 1981-1983; 1985-1987; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 20)
  - NOW New York State Education Task Force, 1976; 1978; 1980-1982; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 21)
  - NOW New York State Employment Task Force and Human Rights, 1978; 1980-1983; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 22)
  - NOW New York State ERA Task Force, 1978-1982; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 23)
  - NOW New York State Executive Committee, 1977-1980 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 24)
  - NOW New York State Executive Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 25)
  - NOW New York State Executive Committee, 1983-1984; 1986; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 26)
  - NOW New York State Financials, 1977-1978; 1982 (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 27)
  - NOW New York State Lesbian Rights Task Force, 1977; 1979-1983; 1985; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 28)
  - NOW New York State Marriage and Divorce Task Force, 1979-1982; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 29)
  - NOW New York State Non-Traditional Task Force, Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 30)
  - NOW New York State Policy, 1977-1983; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 31)
  - NOW New York State PAC Information, 1982-1989; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 32)
  - NOW New York State PAC Information, 1990; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 33)
  - NOW New York State Reproductive Rights Task Force, 1977-1983; 1989; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 34)
  - NOW New York State Task Force on Pornography, 1983-1986; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 35)
  - NOW New York State Task Force on Sexual Assault, Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 36)
  - NOW New York State Task Forces, General, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 37)
  - NOW New York State Women and Aging Task Force, 1978-1979; 1982; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 2 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 38)
  - NOW Policy Manual, 1979 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 1)
  - NOW National Task Forces, 1976-1978; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 2)
  - Northeast Regional NOW Conference, 1976-1978; 1986; 1990 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 3)
  - Position Papers on NOW National Conferences, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 4)
  - Questions for NOW Chapter Activists, 1986 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 5)
  - Resolutions, 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 6)
  - Uniform Dues, 1981 (Box 3 (1-Administrative Files), Folder 7)
- Subject Files, 1971-1999; Undated; 2; 2.75 cubic ft.
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains correspondence, reports, newspaper clippings, newsletters, fact sheets, photographs, brochures and special event materials on a range of topics relevant to the National Organization for Women--Albany, N.Y. Chapter. NOW materials in this series may be from the national, regional, statewide, or local levels. Please note that many national event files, such as the marches and rallies held in Washington, D.C., contain Albany-specific activities and news, including logistics plans for local attendees. The Albany Area Chapter newsletters often feature flyers for special events or other chapter correspondence mailed with or stapled to the respective newsletters. Sometimes the original mock-up for an issue is included. The files entitled "Newspaper Articles of Interest" are newspaper clippings retained and organized by the chapter.
  - Abortion, 1980; 1982-1986 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Abortion, 1987-1989 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Abortion, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Abortion/Choice Clippings, 1988-1989; 1992; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Abortion, Sue Stevens Larsen Speeches, Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Affirmative Action, 1976-1980; 1985-1986; 1996; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - AIDS, 1987-1988 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Albany Area NOW Focus on Equal Education Event, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1973; 1975-1977 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1978-1979 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1982-1983 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1984-1985 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Albany Area NOW Newsletters, 1995-1997; 1999 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Albany Area NOW Susan B. Anthony Raffle, 1992; 1994-1995; 1997-1998; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Albany Area NOW Voter Registration Network, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Albany Area NOW Yellow Pages, 1974; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Albany County Domestic Violence Task Force, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Alternate Work Schedules, 1977 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Assembly Speaker Sheldon Silver, 1997 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Battered Women, 1975-1977; 1981 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Berkshire County NOW Newsletter, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - The Body Politic, National Pro-Choice Directory, 1996 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Campus Organizing, 1993-1994 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Candidate Questionnaires, 1993-1994; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Characteristics of American Children and Youth, 1976 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Charles Andrews Defense Committee, 1983 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Charles Andrews Defense Committee, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Child Care, 1980-1985 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Child Care, 1986-1989; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - "Child Care, A Feminist Perspective", Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Child Support, 1992; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Civil Disobedience Training, 1991-1992; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Civil Rights Restoration Act, 1985-1987; 1989; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Combating Racism Brochure, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Conferences and Workshops, 1977; 1981; 1983 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Consciousness Raising, 1983 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - The Corporate Woman, 1975 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Credit, 1977; 1979; 1981 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Currents, 1993 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Custody, 1982-1986; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Disabled, 1974; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Discrimination, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Divestiture, South Africa, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Domestic Relations, 1984; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Draft, 1980; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Early Childhood Services in New York State, Volumes I and II, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Education, 1977; 1980-1981; 1991; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Education, Sex Bias in Schools, 1974-1975; 1978; 1981; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Employers and Childcare in New York State, 1987 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Equal Education Rights, 1976; 1980; 1984; 1987 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - ERA, 1973; 1976-1977; 1984; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Family, 1979-1980; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Family Planning Advocates of New York State, 1993; 1997; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - The Federal Employees’ Pay Equity Act of 1984 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Fund for the Feminist Majority, 1989-1990 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - "The Future of NOW", 1991 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Handbook for Non-Violent Action, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Hard Questions/Straight Answers: Child Care Policy for New York State, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - High School Speakers Service, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - The History of NOW, 1992; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Homemakers, 1976; 1978-1979; 1985; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - Hooters, 1995; Undated (Box 1 (2-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - Human Rights, Lawsuit, 1994; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - "I Want a Wife", 1992 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Impact of Campus-Based Childcare on the Academic Success of Student-Parents at SUNY Community Colleges, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - "Jail Cries", Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Language, 1979; 1981 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Late-Term Abortions, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Legislative Process, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Lesbian and Gay Rights, 1983; 1987; 1992-1993; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Local New York State NOW Chapter Newsletters, 1988; 1993 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Majority Report, 1973; 1975; 1977 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Making Waves Awards, 1996; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - March for Women's Equality/Women's Lives, Washington, D.C. (April 9, 1989), Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - March for Women's Lives, Washington, D.C. (March 9, 1986), 1985-1986; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Marching Chants, 1983; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Minority and Women Owned Business Development, 1990; 1993; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Minority Women, 1973; 1979; 1981 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Mobilize for Women's Lives, Washington, D.C. (November 12, 1989), 1988-1989; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Mommy Track, 1989 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Nassau NOW, 1993-1994; 1996 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - National Commission on the Observance of International Women's Year Legislation, 1975-1977 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - NOW Guidelines for Supporting Presidential Candidates, Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - NOW National Comments on OJ Simpson, 1995 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - NOW-NJ Newsbreaks, 1993 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - NOW New York State Newsletters, 1976; 1981; 1993 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - NOW New York State Susan B. Anthony Essay Contest, Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - NOW Pamphlets, 1973-1974; 1976-1977; 1979; 2005; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - NOW Photographs, 1986; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - NOW Photographs, Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - NOW Photographs, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - NOW Response to American Psycho, 1990-1991 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - National Women's Conference, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - New York State Legislative and U.S. Congressional Elections, 1982-1984 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - New York State Women's Meeting, 1977 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Newspaper Articles about NOW, 1975-1979; 1985-1988; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Newspaper Articles of Interest, 1981-1982 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Newspaper Articles of Interest, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 34-35)
  - Newspaper Articles of Interest, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Nuclear Power, 1976; 1978-1980; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Operation Rescue, Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Pay Equity, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Pinkster Fest, 1993-1994; 1997 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Phone Banking, 1986; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Pornography, 1984-1987 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Poverty and Women, 1979; 1986; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Pregnancy, 1977-1979; 1981; Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Pro Choice Rally, Albany (January 21, 1990), Undated (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 45)